(Sheldon:)Sometimes your lack of social skills
astonishes me.
(Leonard:)What do you want?
You may wanna sit down.
(Leonard:)I'm in bed.
Point taken. You may wanna sit up.
(Leonard:)Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)I've been seeing Penny
behind your back.
(Penny:)Okay.
When you say "seeing Penny,"
what exactly does that mean?
(Sheldon:)We had dinner last night.
(Sheldon:)She made me spaghetti
with little hot dogs cut up in it.
(Sheldon:)Well, little hot dog.
(Sheldon:)I gave up the other five hot dogs
to a real dog.
(Sheldon:)A real big dog.
(Sheldon:)A hell hound.
It's tangential to the primary story.
How about I circle back to it?
(Leonard:)Fine. Why did you
have dinner with Penny?